＜５年以下の懲役 または➡
50万円以下の
罰金に処せられます＞
＜後悔しても 元には戻せない＞
不正視聴!?
((サスケ : 水月 いずれ お前を
ここから出してやる))
Suigetsu... I will release you from
this place some day.
(水月)やっぱり キミか
キミが ここに来たってことは➡
I knew it was you...
The fact that you're here must mean
you killed Orochimaru.
大蛇丸を倒したんだね。
ああ。
Yeah.
But never mind that.
Let's get you out of here.
そんなことより
ここから出してやる。
(水月)やっと出られた。
Free at last. Thank you, Sasuke.
ありがとう サスケ。
水月 まずは お前だ。
Suigetsu, you're the first.
一緒に来い。
Come with me.
まずは ボクが？
じゃあ 他にもいるの？
Me, first? There are others then?
あと２人 北アジトの重吾と
南アジトの香燐を連れていく。
Two others. I'm taking Jugo
from the northern hideout
and Karin from the southern hideout.
本当に？
Are you sure about that?
なんだ？
What is it?
いやね 好きじゃないから。
アイツら。
It's nothing...
Just that I don't like them.
仲よくは できないなと
そうね 思ってね フフッ。
I can't get along with them...
At least, that's what I think.
ボクを選ぶのは ともかく
あの２人を選ぶキミも➡
Sure, you picked me,
but I wonder about choosing
those two, Sasuke.
どうかと思うよ サスケ。
グダグダうるさい 服を着ろ。
行くぞ。
Enough with the rambling.
Put on your clothes.
We're going.
アハハ！ えらく上からの
もの言いじゃないか。
Ordering me around like a big shot, eh?
キミと ボクの関係を
はっきりさせておこうか ねえ？
Let me clarify the relationship
between you and me...
All right?
悪いけど ボクを助けたのは
キミの都合だ。
Sorry, but you chose  to rescue me.
ボクは キミについて行くなんて
一言も言ってない。
I never said anything about following you.
大蛇丸を倒したからって
キミが上ってわけじゃない。
Just because you defeated Orochimaru
doesn't make you better than me.
Everyone was after him.
みんな 狙っていた。
キミは お気に入りで
監禁されることもなく➡
You were Orochimaru's pet,
so you weren't imprisoned
and you stayed by his side.
大蛇丸の側にいた。
やれるチャンスが みんなよりも
多かっただけだからね。
You had more chances to kill him
than the rest of us.
Gotcha... Just kidding.
なんてね 冗談だよ。
だけど今 キミを見逃したことで➡
But I let you go just now,
so that makes us even.
ボクを助けた貸しは
チャラにしてもらうよ。
I'm free at last,
so I'm going to do as I please.
やっと自由になれたんだ
ボクは ボクの好きにさせてもらう。
そうか 残念だ。
I see.
That's unfortunate.
そういえば キミの小隊だったね。
By the way...
It was your team, wasn't it?
The team that brought down
my great predecessor, Momochi Zabuza.
ボクの大先輩
百地再不斬を倒したのは。
再不斬の刀 首切り包丁って
どうなったのかな？
Whatever happened to his blade...
the Executioner's Blade?
ねぇ こうしようよ。
Let's do this.
If you tell me where the blade is,
and I take possession of it,
キミがそのありかを教えてくれて➡
ボクがその刀を
手に入れることができたら➡
then I'll be willing to help you.
キミを手伝ってもいいよ。
服を着ろ。
Put some clothes on.
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
the "impulses" that makes you want to meet it
aitaku naru no shoudou
the "innocence" that makes you want to cry
nakitaku naru no junjou
they've gone into the summer fire
natsu no hi ni tobikonda
the fireflies aren't coming back
hotaru wa kaeranai
you didn't say a single word and left a kiss for me behind
anata wa nanimo iwazu kuchizuke wo nokoshite
and nodded as you still got burned
kitsuzuku mama unazuita ne
it was so sad that my life was wavering
kanashii hodo inochi yurameiteita
sha la la some day in the future
sha la la itsuka kitto
I will for sure hold it in my hand
boku wa te ni suru nda
it will softly set ablaze
hakanaki mune ni sotto
a light in my empty heart
hikari moeteyuke
sha la la my sweet lovely dear
sha la la itoshiki hito
I can also see you right now
anata mo mieteiru no
the dazzling moon will softly
mabayui tsuki ga sotto
illuminate the morning day
ashita wo terashite
and strongly and strongly shine on
tsuyoku tsuyoku kagayaite
Zabuza's Blade
"GREAT NARUTO BRIDGE"
フン。
なると大橋？
"The Great Naruto Bridge"?
変な名前だね。
What a weird name...
ねぇ 再不斬先輩は強かったかい？
Say, was the great Zabuza-senpai strong?
((カカシ : 全員ふせろ！
Everyone, duck!
It's over.
(カカシ)終わりだ。
I'm not that naïve!
(再不斬)そう甘かねえんだよ！
(サクラ)カカシ先生！
Kakashi-sensei!
《しまった！》
Damn it!
くっ…。
お前らみたいなのは
忍者とは呼ばねえ。
Guys like you aren't called "Ninja"...
(ただのガキだ))
Just mere kids.
どうしたの サスケ。 サスケ！
What's the matter, Sasuke?
Sasuke?
何でもない 行くぞ。
Nothing. Let's go.
はっ…。
ないよ。 ねぇサスケ
ホントにここにあったの？
It's not here.
Say, Sasuke, are you sure it was here?
ああ。
でもないね。 どうしてかな？
Yeah.
But it's not here. I wonder why?
さあな。
オレはその墓の番人じゃない。
How would I know?
I'm not the keeper of that grave.
ないなら
誰かが持って行ったんだろう。
If it's not there,
someone must've taken it.
それはそうだろうね。
ひとりで歩いていくわけないし。
You're right about that.
It wouldn't have walked off on its own.
サスケ 悪いけどあの刀がない以上➡
Sasuke...
Sorry, but without the blade here,
me joining you will have to wait.
キミについて行くのは後回しだね。
どうするつもりだ？
What'll you do then?
What else? I'm gonna look for it.
もちろん 探し出すよ。
忍刀七人衆の刀は➡
The blade of the Seven Ninja Swords
Men of the Mist was passed down
代々受け継がれていくシステムだった。
from generation to generation.
That was the system.
ボクも七人衆に憧れて
修業を積んできたからね。
I aspired to become one of them
and trained for it.
再不斬先輩がいない以上➡
Since Zabuza-senpai is gone...
I'm the one who should possess
that Executioner's Blade.
あの首切り包丁は
ボクが持つべき刀なんだ。
(ゾウリ)どこ見て
歩いてんだ この野郎 バカ野郎！
Watch where you're walking, you idiot!
Huh?
あん？ おうおう 何か
文句でもあんのか にいちゃ…。
What? You have a problem, Nii-chan?
。…ちゃ～に かのんあ
もでくんもかんな うおうお
Ah... whatever...
チッ！ 気をつけろよ！
Just be careful!
What's his problem, stupid...
jerk... old fart... idiot...?!
んだ！ バカ野郎 アホ野郎
アホロートル野郎 ボケ！
優しいなぁ サスケは！
You're so nice, Sasuke...
で このおとしまえは
どうつけてくれるのかな？
So... how're you gonna settle this debt?
Oh...
あぁ！
う～ん フフフ！ ヨーグルト最高！
This yogurt is the best.
こういうの久しぶりなんだぁ！
It's been so long since
I had anything like this.
I was in a water tank all this time.
ずっと水槽のなかにいたからね！
のんびりしていていいのか？
Can you afford to relax like this?
But... you're the one in a rush.
っていうか。
急いでるのは
キミのほうなんだろ？
Why're you gathering us
together anyway?
いったい ボクらを集めて
どうするつもり？
３人が揃ったときに話す。
I'll tell you when we've all assembled.
ふ～ん。 よ～し！
天下でもとっちゃおう！
"All right, let's go conquer this world!"
You're not gonna say something
like that, are you?
なんて言い出したりして！
Do that on your own time.
そんなものは
お前たちで好きにしろ。
I'm aiming for...
something much bigger.
オレがとるものは…。
もっとでかい。
他のヤツがそんな話をしても
まったく信じられないけど➡
If anyone else started saying that,
I wouldn't believe it for a second.
キミが言うとね～。
But with you...
I think maybe it's possible...
And that's the strange thing.
ホントなのかなって思えるのが
不思議だよね。
あっ ねぇ キミ。
なると大橋だったっけ？
Oh say...
The Great Naruto Bridge, was it?
あの橋の近くに➡
Ever heard of a large blade
near that bridge?
大きな刀があったの
知らないかい？
Well... Oh, maybe there was...
はぁ ええ。
そういえばあったような。
それが？
What about it?
彼が その刀を探しているんだ。
He's looking for that blade.
Huh?! S-Someone might know about it...
I'll go and ask!
えぇっ!?
あ あの 誰か知ってるかも！
聞いてきます！ や～ん！
Oh dear!
"SCREAMS"
You're quite the ladies' man, eh?
キミってモテるんだね！
I know!
- Tazuna-san...
- Who lives by the riverside...
川辺に住んでる！
タズナさんなら！
...would know!
知ってるんじゃないでしょうか！
タズナか…。
Tazuna... huh?
Who is this Tazuna?
誰 タズナって？
The carpenter boss who built that bridge.
あの橋をつくった
大工の頭領だ。
頭なら今はいないぜ。
The boss isn't here right now.
どこに行ったのかな？
Do you know where he went?
To the Land of Lightning to build a bridge.
He took Inari with him.
雷の国だよ。 橋の工事に
イナリを連れて出かけてらぁ。
He won't be back for another year.
あと１年は帰ってこねえよ！
The Land of Lightning, eh?
That's very far.
カミナリの国かぁ 遠いな。
Do you know of a large blade that
was left near the Great Naruto Bridge?
なると大橋の近くに➡
大きな刀があったのを
知らないか？
Oh, that.
ああ あれね。
Daikoku Tenzen took it.
大黒天善が持っていったんだよ。
He originally came here to capture
the Ninja who wielded the blade.
本当は あの刀を使っていた忍者を
捕まえに来たんだけど➡
死んでるってんで
代わりにあの刀を➡
But after learning the Ninja was dead,
he took the blade with him instead.
持っていったんだってよ。
Damn it... Daikoku Tenzen, eh?
まいったなぁ。
大黒天善か…。
水の国の大名の
側近だったヤツだよ。
He was the aide to
the lord of the Land of Water.
Apparently, many of his men were killed
再不斬先輩が霧隠れで
クーデターを起こしたとき➡
during Zabuza-senpai's coup d'état
in the Hidden Mist.
ずいぶんと
手下がやられたらしいよ。
I guess he had a grudge from back then.
そのことを
根にもっていたんだなぁ。
テメエ どこに目をつけて…！
Where the hell...
do you think you're--?!
Hey, we were just looking for you.
やあ！ キミのこと➡
ちょうど捜してたんだ！
うわっ!!
うわ～っ!!
な… 何なんだよ オメエら!?
Wh-Who are you guys?!
You seem like the type to know
all kinds of things...
だって キミ
裏事情とか詳しそうだし。
オレは 天善のことなんて
知らねえよ！
I know nothing about Tenzen!
Anything will do.
Just tell us what you know.
知ってることだけでいいんだけど
話してくれないかな？
あ… あっ…。
(ゾウリ)だ… 大黒天善は
政治家だが それは表の顔で➡
D-Daikoku Tenzen is a politician...
But there's another side to him.
He's the boss of a huge band of thieves.
裏じゃ 大盗賊団を率いる頭領だ。
巨額のワイロを 大名に渡して➡
I hear he doles out huge bribes
to the feudal lords,
好き放題に
悪事を働いてるって話だ。
and gets to do whatever
evil things he likes.
See, you know it all. And?
Where does he live?
ちゃんと知ってるじゃん。
で どこに住んでるの？
Just to the south...
there's a castle in the forest.
(ゾウリ)南の外れ
森の中に建つ城だ。
Rumor says several thousand mercenaries
guard the place and that it's impenetrable.
その城は 数千の傭兵に守られて
難攻不落だってウワサだ。
(天善)うん!?
だ… 誰だ!? どこから入った？
Wh-Who's there? How did you get in?!
明後日 数万の兵を引き連れ
この城を落としにくる。
The day after tomorrow,
this castle will be attacked by
tens of thousands of soldiers.
ありったけの兵隊を集めておけ。
Make sure you gather
every man available.
My name... is Suigetsu.
オレの名は… 水月。
(天善)曲者だ!!
出あえ！ 出あえ！
An intruder! Men! Come out!
(水月)まったく…。
Cripes... What's going on?
どうなってんだよ？
It seems another powerful clan plans
to attack Tenzen's castle tomorrow
明日 他の豪族が
数万の軍勢を引き連れて➡
with an army that numbers
in the tens of thousands.
天善の城に攻め込むらしい。
へえ～ それ ホントなの？
Oh... is that true?
あ～あ… まあ いっか。
Oh well, whatever.
敵が混乱すれば
チャンスは増えるし➡
The more confused the enemy becomes,
the better my chances.
Be it several thousand
or tens of thousands,
千人が万人になろうと
忍者であるボクには関係ないしね。
it doesn't matter to a Ninja like me.
首切り包丁は 今夜にでも
忍び込んでとってくるよ。
I'll sneak in tonight and
take the Executioner's Blade.
ひとつ 賭けをしないか？
How about making a wager?
賭け？
A wager...?
どちらが先に
首切り包丁を手に入れるか。
On who gets
the Executioner's Blade first...
アハハ！ キミに そんな遊び心が
あるなんて思わなかったよ。
Huh?! I never expected you
to have a playful side!
やろうよ。 おもしろそうだ。
Let's do it. It sounds like fun.
では 今からだ。
Then it starts now.
There's only one rule.
We don't kill anyone.
ルールは ひとつ。
誰ひとり殺さぬこと。
えっ？
Huh?
なんだ キサマは！
Who the hell are you?!
You're suspicious!
怪しいヤツめ！
キミ… 今からって…。
You mean... Now as in...?
ホント 今からなんだね。
It really starts now, huh?
フゥ… 賭けに
負けるわけにはいかないし…。
I can't lose this wager.
Well, all right, let's do it.
いいよ つきあうよ。
フゥ…。
Fire Style: Fireball Jutsu!
火遁 豪火球の術！
ひょ～ さすがサスケ！
Gotta hand it to you, Sasuke!
…って お前！ いないのかよ!?
What the--?! He's gone?!
(みんな)うお～！
Is this for real?!
マジですか？
(みんな)うお～！
Damn, may as well get started!
くっ！ いっちょいくか！
でやっ！
フゥ… さすがに疲れるね。
やっとゴールだ。
This is tiring, after all.
Finally, my goal.
Impossible... You defeated
all those men by yourself?!
バカな… あれだけの軍勢を
たった一人で倒したのか!?
Well yeah. Even with legitimate weapons,
attacking me is useless.
まあね。
ボクには まともな武器できても
無意味だから。
くっ…！
If legitimate weapons are of no use...!
まともな武器でダメなら
こいつは どうだ～!!
How about... this?!
Say, that's my Executioner's Blade.
あっ！ そいつは
ボクの首切り包丁じゃないか！
Ah, you did it!
おお！ やったか!?
You let down your guard at the very end.
最後の最後で油断しおったな。
フハハハハハッ！
(水月)ハハハハ！
おっ!?
Sorry. Blades don't work on me...
ごめんね。
ボクには刃物は通用しないんだよ。
ねっ。
You see?
But I'm jealous.
でも うらやましいよ。
You're able to wield that blade
without any special training...
特別な訓練がなくても
その刀を振り回せるなんて。
It helps when you have a good physique.
体格がいいと得だよね。
うっ… ぬお～！
うっ！
町で言いふらしているんだって？
I hear you've been telling
everyone in town...
That you killed the Demon Zabuza
and took that blade from him.
鬼人 再不斬を殺して
その刀を奪ったんだ って。
Th-That wasn't me...
It was Tenzen-sama who...
そ… それは
オレではなく天善様が…。
Hmm... So you killed Zabuza-senpai?
へぇ～ アンタが再不斬先輩をね。
N-No... The one who killed Zabuza was...
ち… 違う！
再不斬をやったのは…！
Zabuza?
再不斬？
Err... no! The one who killed Zabuza-san
wasn't me...
(天善)あぁ～ いや！
再不斬さんを殺したのは➡
オレじゃなくて その… うっ！
お前は 昨日の…。
You're... the one... from yesterday!
He's the one!
He's the one who killed Zabuza-san!
あっ！ アイツだ！
アイツが 再不斬さんを殺したんだ！
All I did was bring the blade
back from the grave!
オレは その刀を
墓から持ってきただけだ！
グッ！ フハハハハ！
くしくも０点じゃないよ！
I'll give you some points for that.
That's a pretty good lie for a villain
like you to come up with.
悪党が とっさについたウソにしちゃ
気が利いてる。
ハハハハハハ！
Suigetsu!
水月。
How thoughtful.
I was feeling a bit dehydrated.
気が利くね ちょっと
脱水症状気味だったんだよね。
勘違いしてるようだけど➡
I think you're under
the wrong impression here.
I wasn't particularly close to Zabuza-san.
ボクと再不斬さんとは
べつに親しくも何ともないんだよ。
But the thought of my Senpai
from my village...
ただね同郷の先輩がね。
うお～!!
うわぁ～!!
...having such pathetic rumors about
losing to weaklings like you is...
こんな弱っちい連中に
やられたなんて➡
無様なウワサを
たてられるのも… なんてね。
You know...?
キサマら こんなことをして
ただで済むと思ってるのか。
D-Do you think you can
get away with this?!
おとしまえは つけないとねえ。
Well, you'll have to pay for this... right?
アンタで試し切りをさせてもらうよ。
ひっ!?
I think I'll test it on you.
Forget it. What's the sense
in killing someone like him?
やめておけ
そんなヤツを斬って何になる。
フッ。
ああ!!
I've cut through the main pillars,
so you'd better get out of here.
大黒柱を斬ったから
早くここから出たほうがいいよ。
I'll spare your life.
命だけは助けてあげる。
Out of respect for you, Sasuke.
サスケに免じてね。
サスケ？ まさか
あの大蛇丸を殺った サスケなのか？
Sasuke? Not that...?!
Sasuke who killed Orochimaru?!
Say, you're famous.
They know your name even around here.
へえ キミって有名人なんだね。
こんなとこまで
名前が響いているなんてさ。
うぅ… うお！
ああ～!!
ハハハハハハハ！
フフ この刀があれば
キミにも負けない… かもね。
As long as I have this blade,
I won't even lose to you... maybe.
Say... You knew that I was going
to claim this blade, didn't you?
あのさ キミ ボクが刀欲しいって
言い出すとわかってたんでしょ。
And... You knew from the start
that the blade wasn't in that grave...
それに 最初から あの墓に
刀がないことも知っていた。
I see...
そうか。
The one who warned that castle
to gather its men...
わざわざ あの城に兵隊集めさせる
情報を流したのも➡
was you?
キミ？
Tenzen acted like he'd met you before.
天善 キミと会ったような
口ぶりだったし。
Hey? Did you suggest a wager just
to lure me into enemy territory?
なに 賭けとか言ったのも➡
わざわざ ボクを敵のただ中に
追い込むため？
もしかして試したの？
このボクを。
Were you just testing me?
Man, you're terrible.
What if I was hurt?
ハハッ ひどいことするな。
ケガでもしたら
どうするつもりだよ。
でも これでよくわかったよ
キミって人がさ。
Well, I understand now...
what kind of guy you are.
And you're exactly the way
I imagined you to be.
まあ それでこそ
ボクのイメージどおりのサスケだよ。
刀は手に入れたから
約束どおり力は貸すけどさ。
Anyway, I have my blade.
So I'll help you as promised.
So? Which way do we go? Oh wait...
…で どっちから行くの？
あっ 待って
近いほうからだよね。
The nearest route, right?
That would be your answer.
キミのことは
少しわかってきたんだ。
I'm starting to figure you out...
それがキミらしい答えだし。
フッ そう 近いほうからだ。
Right, the nearest route.
ぐわ～!!
(香燐)大蛇丸が死んだからって
勝手されちゃ困るんだよ！
Just because Orochimaru
is dead doesn't mean
I'll let you have your way!
The feeling of this Chakra...
I-It can't be...
《このチャクラの感じ ま まさか…》
before the reality of a deep breath
sonzai to shinkokyuu no genjitsu wo mae ni
my gaze my very existence tries to challenge it
idomou to suru shisen wa
mistakes are made and in the confusion of it all everything burns into my mind
machigai mo tomadoi mo zenbu yaki tsukeru
in a series of moments
isshun no renzoku no naka de
beyond a great number of promises
ikutsu mono yakusoku no sono ue ni tatte wa
are the words that spilled over from the day as I reflect upon them
kamishimeru ano hi koboreochita kotoba
it's as though I made a vow which expresses these feelings into words
komerareta omoi wa chikai no you de
then it would link the befinning with the present day
kuchi ni sureba ima to hajimari wo tsunagu
it's not in my dreams
yume de wa nakute
that place doesn't exist in a fantasy world either
esoragoto no sekai de mo nai basho de sa
before the reality of a deep breath
sonzai to shinkokyuu no genjitsu no mae ni
my gaze my very existence tries to challenge it
idomou to suru shisen wa
mistakes are made and in the confusion of it all everything burns into my mind
machigai mo tomadoi mo zenbu yaki tsukete
embracing the long path ahead
sono zutto saki wo toraeru
in a series of moments
isshun no renzoku no naka de
Next Episode
Say... Why are you gathering men?
＜港町 ハルジオン。
I have a goal...
今 ここを出港した
フェアリーテイルの船があった。
And I have a better chance of
achieving it with a small team.
But still,
I don't know about choosing Karin...
８組の魔導士たちを乗せ➡
Unlike me,
she's a follower of Orochimaru.
いざ 天狼島へ＞
Not to mention her personality...
But, her power is special...
Well... That I'll have to agree with you on.
Guardian of the
Iron Wall
Next time: "Guardian of the Iron Wall"